Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of grants, publications, and other projects, circa 1976-1990; Accession 1994-A-004
  - Walter Camp Project: Staff memo's on processing and microfilming, 6/79-1/82 (Box 1)
  - Architectural archives: correspondence, 10/78-6/80 (Box 1)
  - Architectural Archives: information on other institutions and programs, 1970s (Box 1)
  - Architectural Archives: NEH Grant, RC-30645-7~-412, 10/1/1978-3/31/79, 8/77-3/80 (Box 1)
  - Architectural Archives: NHPRC grant application and correspondence, 2/77-8/81 (Box 1)
  - Architectural Archives Project: NEH grant application and correspondence, 7/77-11/80 (Box 1)
  - Architectural Archives: NEH grant, RC-30645-78-4:2, 2/1/1978-7/31/79 extended to 9/30/1979, 3/78-11/79 (Box 1)
  - Architectural Archives: re: publication of The Buildings of Yale University 1977 (Box 1)
  - Architecture Census Project, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Clearwater Publishing Company -Latin American Pamphlet Collection, 1/84-11/86 (Box 1)
  - John Collier -Project MCA (includes only a cross reference sheet), 0 (Box 1)
  - Y/C/S grant: Second extension of Year II 1/86-6/86, 12/85-6/86 (Box 1)
  - Y/C/S grant: Site Visit 9/19/85, 31291 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: Extension of Year II 4/85-12/85, 9/84-8/85 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: Final Report to the Office of Education 1/1/83-3/31/84, 4/84-3/85 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: Invoice for RLIN service (Yale), 12/83-12/85 (Box 1)
  - C/s/Y grant: extension of Yr I 4/84-12/84, 10/83-12/83 (Box 1)
  - RLG: Rates for service from the Research Libraries Information Network 9/1/86 -, 31594 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: condition of award for Yr II, 1984Jan-Dec, 6/83-8/83 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: application for Yr II, revised budget submitted 6/83, 30468 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: application for Yr II, worksheets for budget revisions 5/83, 30437 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: Invoices from C/S/RLG 1983 -, 1/83-9/86 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: Quarterly Reports to the Office of Education 1/1/83-, 5/83-11/83 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: Conditions of award fo= Year I, 1983 Jan-Dec, 6/82-6/83 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: application for Year II, 1984 Jan-Dec, filed 11/82, 10/82-11/82 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: carr. and memos for preparation of Yr. II grant appl. submitted 11/82, 1/83-12/84 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: 31, 1984 REVISED 5/17/82 Jan 1, 1983 -March, 5/82-7/82 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: corres. &memos for application revised 5/82 -6/82, 30072 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: 1982 Feb -application for: Jan 1, 1983 -Dec 31, 1984, 29983 (Box 1)
  - C/S/Y grant: Corres. &memos for preparation of appl. submitted 2/82, 12/81-2/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated Cataloging grant: Latin American Pamphlet Collection, efforts to continue project, 10/82-11/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Financial status report (final) 6/30/83, 10/80-6/83 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Final report to Office of Education Jan 1~ 1982 -March 31, 1983, 30407 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Final report to Office of Education Yr I 1981 Jan-Dec, 2/81-12/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Approved budget Year II - 1982 Jan - Dec, 11/81-11/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: extention of Yr. ~ 1st 1/82 &2nd 11/82, 0 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Notice of award for Yr. I., 1980 Oct 1 - 1981 Sep 30, 6/80-9/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Notice of a~ard fc= Yr. II (1/1/82-3/31/83), terms and conditions, 7/81-1/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: RLG financial repcrt for external design phase 7/1/82 - 2/28/83, 30407 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: RLG Task Force, application for funding, 2/81-5/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: original application for Yrs. I &II, draft and worksheets 1980 Feb, 9/79-6/80 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: me~os, notes, working papers, 1980-, 11/80-3/81 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: RLG Task Force, correspondence, minutes, reports, 11/80-9/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Qua=terly reports to office of Education 1981-82, 6/81-10/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Correspondence with u.s. Dept. of Educ. (Frank Steve~s, Paul Krakes) 1980-, 10/80-10/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: correspondence with archivists and RLG 1980-1981, 7/79-2/82 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Application {final version) for Yr. II 1982 Ja= 1 - Dec 31, 29768 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: Application for Yr.II, 1982 Jan-Dec (NOT APPRO~~D), 29646 (Box 1)
  - Automated cataloging grant: original application for Yrs. I &II (1980 oct 1 - 1981 Sep 3C} 1980 Feb, 2/79-2/80 (Box 1)
  - Preservation &Subject Guice Project: NEW Title II C grant proposal, 11/77-8/78 (Box 1)
  - Preservation &Subject Guice Project: Guide Project Prospectus 1978, 11/77-7/80 (Box 1)
  - HEW: Title II-C Grant guidelines, 29342 (Box 1)
  - C M C B P: NIB Grant application correspondence 1980-1982, 10/81-9/82 (Box 1)
  - C M C B P: NIB grant application, site visits &corres. 1976-77, 1/76-8/77 (Box 1)
  - C M C B P: NIH grant application - Terminal Progress Report 1982, 1/82-7/82 (Box 1)
  - C M C H P: NIH grant applicatication &correspodence 1978-79 (Box 2)
  - C M C H P: NIH grant applicatication and correspondence 1974-75, 6/74-8/60 (Box 2)
  - C M C H P: NIH grant: Application for year 3, 12/1/80 - 11/30/81, and notice of award, 9/79-9/80 (Box 2)
  - C M C H P: (NIH grant 1 608 LMO 3072): application for second year, 12/1/79-11/30/80, &notice of award, 10/79-4/80 (Box 2)
  - C M C H P: (NIH Grant 1 608 LMO 3072): NIH policy, NIH application form for continuation, 3/77-7/79 (Box 2)
  - C M C H P: (NIH grant. NLM-EMP 1 G08 L~ 03072-01): Notice of award 12/1/78 - 11/30/81, 11/78-11/80 (Box 2)
  - C M C H P: NIH Grant publicity, resource list, memos 12/1/78 - 11/30/79, 7/76-12/78 (Box 2)
  - contemporary Records Model Grant Application for period 7/1/80 to 6/30/82, NEPRC 1980 Feb, 12/79-7/80 (Box 2)
  - HOUSE DIARIES PROJECT: PUBLICATIO~ (agreement with MCA), 12/78-2/79 (Box 2)
  - HOUSE DIARIES PROJECT: Correspondence 1978-, 5/78-10/83 (Box 2)
  - HOUSE DIARIES PROJECT: Proposal to NHPRC 1977 Award of Grant #78-4 1977 Oct 1 - 1978 Sep 30, 10/77-10/79 (Box 2)
  - HOUSE DIARIES PROJECT: Renewal of Grant #78-137 '1978 Oct 1 - 1979 Sep 30, 4/78-4/80 (Box 2)
  - HOUSE DIARIES PROJECT: Extension of 1st year Grant to 12/31/78, 9/78-1/79 (Box 2)
  - HOUSE DIARIES PROJECT: Planning correspondence 1975-77, 11/75-10/77 (Box 2)
  - HOUSE DIARIES PROJECT: Financial status report forms and instructions, 11/77-10/78 (Box 2)
  - History of Medicine Collection: correspcndence 1982 -, 30195 (Box 2)
  - History of Medicine Collection: srant application to NLM Medical Lib. Resource Project 1982 June, 6/82-2/85 (Box 2)
  - History of Medicine Collection: Notes &general information for prepari~g proposal, 10/80-5/82 (Box 2)
  - Medical History Collection: Grant proposal to NEH, 1984 May 17, 30803 (Box 2)
  - MICROFILM CORPORATION OF AMERICA, 4/77-12/8 (Box 2)
  - Preservation and Subject Guide Project Title IEC: subject Guice to Manuscript Collections 1981 (Box 2)
  - Preservation &Subject Guide Project HEW Title IIC Grant extension 10/1/80 - 6/30/81, 9/80-6/81 (Box 2)
  - Preservation &Subject Guide Project: HEW Title IIC grant quarterly reports, 1/79-4/80 (Box 2)
  - Preservation &subject Guide Project: HEW Title IIC grant, annual report for 10/1/78 - 9/30/79, 29190 (Box 2)
  - Preservation &Subject Guide Project: HEW Title I:C MSS &Archives Project Report, 12/78-11/79 (Box 2)
  - Preservation &Subject Guide Project: HEW Title IIC grant 10/1/79 - 9/30/80, 2/79-10/79 (Box 2)
  - Preservatior. &Subject Guide Project: HEW Title IIC EquipmentPurchases, 6/77-9/78 (Box 2)
  - Preservatior. &Subject Guide Project: HEW Title IIC grant 10/1/78 - 9/30/79, 8/78-12/78 (Box 2)
  - HEW Title II C (Fiche of report) Publicity Award - 10/80 - 12/80, 9/80-7/82 (Box 2)
  - Records Survey, Yale: Information on other archival and record magement programs, 5/78-2/79 (Box 2)
  - Records Survey, Yale: Hemo from Henry Chauncey, Secretary, to University offices 1978, 6/78-11/78 (Box 2)
  - Records Survey, Yale: MSS&Archives discussions with Yale admistrators, proposal by L. Dowler (8/76) 1975-78, 11/75-5/80 (Box 2)
  - RECORDS SURVEY, YALE: Reports &Miscellaneous Information, 9/77-8/80 (Box 2)
  - Records Survey, Yale: NHPRC Grant #79-3, starting date 10/1/78, 7/78-5/80 (Box 2)
  - Records Survey, Yale: NPRC Grant application and correspondence, 1/78-4/78 (Box 2)
  - RECORDS SURVEY, YALE: Financial status report forns &instructions, 28764 (Box 2)
  - RECORDS SURVEY: RESEARCH ON HUMAN SUBJECTS: FAS Committee, 2/78-12/79 (Box 2)
  - RLIN/AMC workstation, Yale/RLG Proposal to Title IIC, 31352 (Box 2)
  - UNI VERS ITY MICROFILM INTERNTL., 5/85-2/90 (Box 2)
  - Video Archive for Holocaust Testimonies, 1984, 1/84-4/84 (Box 2)
  - Video archive for Holocaust Testimonies, 1982-83, 4/82-9/83 (Box 2)
  - whiting Foundaticn - s. Rosenstock 1986, 12/85-1/87 (Box 2)
  - Yale-China assn.: deed of gift of the Yale-China Assn. Records to Yale and related correspondence, 6/79-6/80 (Box 2)
  - Yale-China Assn.: NHPRC grant application and correspondence 1976-1979, 5/76-3/80 (Box 2)
  - Yale-China Assn.: NEPRC grant 79-144 6 month report, 4/30/80, 11/79-10/80 (Box 2)
  - Yale-China Assn.: NHPRC Grant #79-144, 11/1/79 10/31/80, 11/79-10/80 (Box 2)
  - Yale-China photograph Archives Final Report - April, 30042 (Box 2)
- Reports, financial/budget, memoranda, personnel and various subject files, 1965-1990; Accession 1994-A-062
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1964 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1965 May (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1966 May (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1967 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1968 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1969 June 30 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1970 June 30 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1971 June 30 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1972 May (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports: Librarian (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: notes, statistics, drafts May 1972 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1973 May 30 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: notes, statistics, 26785 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1974 May 30 (Box 1)
  - Report on public services activities in MSS & Archives June 1973-May 1974 (Box 1)
  - Draft ofannual report and statistical 1973-74 summaries of departmental activities (Box 1)
  - Professional activities: MSS & Archives 1973-74 Staff (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1974-75 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1976 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1975-76 (Box 1)
  - Statistical summaries of departmental activities, 1975-76 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1977 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1976-77 (Box 1)
  - Statistical summaries of departmental activities for annual report, 1976-77 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1978 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1977-78 (Box 1)
  - Statistical summaries of departmental activities for annual report, 1977-78 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1979 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Summaries of departmental activities for annual report, 1978-79 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1980 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Summaries of departmental activities for annual report, 1979-80 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1981 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Summaries of departmental activities for the annual report, 1980-81 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1982 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Summaries of departmental activities for annual report, 1981-82 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1983 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Summaries of departmental activities for the annual report, 1982-83 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1984 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Summaries of departmental activities for the annual report, 1983-84 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1985 May 31 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report: Summaries of departmental activities, 1984-85 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1986 May 31 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report: Summaries of departmental activities, 1985-86 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1987 June 30 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report: Summaries of departmental activities, 1986-87 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report, 1987-88 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report: Unit Report Public Services, 1987-88 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report: Unit Reports: VART/ University Archives, 1987-88 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report: Unit Reports: Public Services/ Technical Services, 1988-89 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report: Unit Reports: VART/ University Archives, 1988-89 (Box 2)
  - Public Services Annual Report, FY 1988-89 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report for the year ending 1989 June 30 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report, 1988-89 (Box 2)
  - Yale University Library: Visitor affiliation list, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report, 1989-90 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report, 1990-91 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report, 1991-92 (Box 2)
  - Annual Statistical Summary: blank copies (Box 2)
  - Quarterly Statistical Report (Box 2)
  - Reports: Accession 1969 (Box 2)
  - Reports: Monthly Statistics 1969 (Box 2)
  - Reports: Weekly Statistics 1969 (Box 2)
  - Statistics (Box 2)
  - Financial/Budget and Equipment (Box 2)
  - Equipment and Supplies 1969-1972 (Box 3)
  - Equipment Budget (Box 3)
  - Equipment Correspondence (Box 3)
  - Equipment requests 1989-1992 (Box 3)
  - Equipment Suggestions (Box 3)
  - Expense Budget Sheets, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
  - Financial (Box 3)
  - Financial Accounts/Supplies (Box 3)
  - Financial Retrenchment 1977 (Box 3)
  - _Operating Budget 1979-1980 (Box 3)
  - Pierson Fund (Box 3)
  - Record ofProcessing Supplies Ordered 1974 (Box 3)
  - Supplies-Major Processing 1974 (Box 3)
  - Supplies (Box 3)
  - Supplies (Box 3)
  - Supplies Sold to other Depts. (Box 3)
  - Supply Card File, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Supply Logs by Account No., 1979-1980 (Box 3)
  - Supply Logs by Ace. NO., 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - Supply Logs by Ace. No., 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - Supply Logs by Ace. No., 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - Telephone Equipment, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Xerox Duplicating (Box 3)
  - Yale University Telephone Statements, 1990 (Box 3)
  - 802B-50-87362/ycc Word Process. Costs, 1981 (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-00001 (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-55622/Video Archive (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-57966/Yale China Ass. (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-74440IBowles (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-74482/Jovanovich (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-74506/Lindbergh Equipment (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-74507/Lindbergh Gift (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-74565/Sigerist (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-75385/Rogers Limited Use Acc. (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-87484/Stimson Award (Box 3)
  - 802A-50-87981/Records (Box 3)
  - SurveyFinancial/Travel (Box 3)
  - Business Travel (Box 4)
  - Professional Travel Grants, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
  - SAA Nashville Convention (Box 4)
  - YUL Travel Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Administrative Memos (Box 5)
  - Beinecke Memos 1968-80 (Box 5)
  - Beinecke Special Collections 1970-72 (Box 5)
  - Bibliography Department Bollier, John 1984-85 (Box 5)
  - Librarian's Office Daly, Radley H. 1968-83 lof2 (Box 5)
  - Librarian's Office Daly, Radley H. 20f2 (Box 5)
  - Manuscripts and Archives Dowler, Lawrence 1975-82 (Box 5)
  - Librarian's Office Engley, Donald 1973-82 (Box 5)
  - Librarian's Office Harrison, John A. 1976-77 (Box 5)
  - Kahn, Herman 1970-80 Folder 1 of4 (Box 5)
  - Kahn, Herman 1970-80 Folder 2 of4 (Box 5)
  - Kahn, Herman 1970-80 Folder 3 of4 (Box 5)
  - Kahn, Herman 1970-80 Folder 4 of 4 (Box 5)
  - Misc. Memos (Box 5)
  - Misc. Memos 1968 (Box 5)
  - Mudd Library, Steeley G. 1979-82 (Box 5)
  - Librarian's Office Rogers, Rutherford 1969-84 (Box 5)
  - Attendance Procedures, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Contract Negotiations and Strike Preparedness, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Contract Negotiations and Strike Preparedness, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Contract Negotiations and Strike Preparedness, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Contract Implementation, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Contract Negotiations, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Library Task Force-Contract Implementation, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Local 34 (Box 6)
  - Local 34 Contract, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Local 34 Contract, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Management in Unionized Environment-Literature (Box 6)
  - Strikes (Box 6)
  - Union Organization Activities (Box 7)
  - Administrative Assitant VI, 31998 (Box 7)
  - KDM-MCL Admin. Asst. Search April 1987 (Box 7)
  - Informal Archival Candidates (Box 7)
  - Archives Asst: Technical Service (Box 7)
  - Archivist 4-87: 2 Year Term Search (Box 7)
  - Archivist I (Box 7)
  - Archivist Info Systems (Box 7)
  - Archivist Librarian I (Box 7)
  - Head of Technical Services (Box 7)
  - Incomplete (Box 7)
  - Internal (Box 7)
  - L-I Job Description (Box 7)
  - MSS&A. Temp for Secretarial duties To 10-18-91 (Box 7)
  - Public Services Assistant III Exempt vs Non-Exempt status (Box 7)
  - Public Services Archivist (Box 7)
  - Search: Head of Technical Services (Box 7)
  - Search: University Archivist/ Asst. Head (Box 7)
  - Yes (Box 7)
  - Search: Asst. Personnel Librarian (Box 7)
  - Evaluations-Letters ofRecommendation (Box 8)
  - Flex-Time, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Managerial Job Audit, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Orientation to MSS & A for new YUL Staff, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Performance Expectations LI, LII (Box 8)
  - Performance Evaluations (Box 8)
  - Personnel (Box 8)
  - Personnel-PCPP, 1966-I971 (Box 8)
  - Personnel Policy (Box 8)
  - Sarason Study ofLibrarians, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Schedules (Box 8)
  - StaffDevelopment-Supervisors (Box 8)
  - Work Study Students, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Yale Univ. Undergrad. Internship Program-Report (Box 8)
  - Subject Files (Box 8)
  - Admin. Organization (Box 9)
  - African Coll. Karis Project, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Alcohol Interview Guide Material (Box 9)
  - Articles and Notes (Box 9)
  - Articles for Yale Alumni Magazine (Box 9)
  - Beinecke Hole (Box 9)
  - Bookplate (Box 9)
  - CMCHPC (Box 9)
  - Copyright (Box 9)
  - Ezra Stiles Project (Box 9)
  - Ezra Stiles NHPRC Project, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
  - Chester Group (Box 9)
  - CT Assessment Report-Draft, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Dealers, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Early Departmental Records (Box 9)
  - Exhibit-Prudential Letters, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Exhibits-Cases, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Federal Archives and Records Center (Box 9)
  - Georgia (Box 9)
  - Fred C. Kelly Papers (Box 9)
  - Hammermill Paper Co. (Box 9)
  - Hist. MSS & A Research Notes, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Law Lib. Business (Box 9)
  - Libraries and Historical Societies (Box 9)
  - Manuscript Society (Box 9)
  - Manuscripts and Archives-Publicity (Box 9)
  - Manuscripts at Yale, 1957-1968 (Box 9)
  - Manuscripts Processing-Move (Box 9)
  - Medical (Box 9)
  - Memorabilia (Box 9)
  - Move II (Box 9)
  - MSS & A Orbis, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Orbis Issues (Box 9)
  - PAce, 1991 (Box 9)
  - PACC, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - YULPACe, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - PACC Five Year Plan (Box 9)
  - YULPACC, 1988 (Box 9)
  - YUL PACC. RLG Review, 1988 (Box 9)
  - PACC, 1987 (Box 9)
  - PACC (Box 9)
  - PACC (Box 9)
  - President's Office-Vault Inventory (Box 9)
  - Publicity-Collections Rohert F. Metzdorf (Box 9)
  - Rules for Use ofMaterials (Box 10)
  - Stimson Papers (Box 10)
  - Translation Services, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Trips (Box 10)
  - Vault 107 (Box 10)
  - YUL Collection Develop., 1990 (Box 10)
  - YUL Coll. Dev. Group Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Yale Architectural Records, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Yale Archives, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Yale Daily News, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Yale Merl. School Dev. Office, 1986 (Box 10)
  - YU Archives, 1989 (Box 10)
  - YU Archives-Accession List, 1989 (Box 10)
  - YU Archives 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - YU Archives-Proposal for Archives Committee, 1990 (Box 10)
  - YU Archives-Cost to the Library Discussions, 1991 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Interlibrary Loan, 1987 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Latin American Pamphlet Collection, 1989 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Map Resources (Box 10)
  - YUL-Personnel Info. Exchange, 1989 (Box 10)
  - YUL-PersonneIOffice-Meetings, 1987 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Photographic Services, 1986 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Preservation Survey, 1986 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Reprint Agreements, 1988 (Box 10)
  - YUL-SML Reference (Box 10)
  - YUL-Tech. Services Reorganization Plan, 1988 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Notis Acquisitions, 1987 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Notis. Orbis Terminal Allocation (Box 10)
  - YUL-Orbis, 1990 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Orbis, 1989 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Orbis Serials Check-In, 1990 (Box 10)
  - YUL-Task Force on Retrospective Conversion (Box 10)
  - Policies and Procedures, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Accessions Procedures (Box 11)
  - Access Policy (Box 11)
  - Acquisition Policy, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Criteria for Auto. Transfer of Titles to Beinecke, 1973 (Box 11)
  - General Policies and Procedures, 1966-1983 (Box 11)
  - Manuscripts-General Policies, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Manuscript Procedures and Forms, 1969 (Box 11)
  - MSS & A Procedures (Box 11)
  - Statement ofPolicy ofYU Archives, 1972 (Box 11)
  - YU Archives-Review, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Yale University Press Books for Manuscripts and Archives Policy (Box 11)
  - Job Descriptions (Box 11)
  - Job Classification, 1970, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Job Descriptions (Box 12)
  - Job Descriptions-MSS, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Job Descriptions-MSS & A., 1974 (Box 12)
  - Job Descriptions-MSS & A, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Job Descriptions (Box 12)
  - Job Descriptions-MSS & A., 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - Job Descrip.-Current (Box 12)
  - Public Services Job Descrip. (Box 12)
  - Public Services Reorganization-Job, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Descrip. (Box 12)
  - YU Human Resources-Job Class. and, 1989 (Box 12)
  - YUL-Performance Expectations and (Box 12)
  - Promotion Review Policy (Box 12)
  - Current Job Descriptions (Box 13)
  - Sterling Memorial Library (Box 13)
  - Wisconsin Historical Society, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Facilities/Space (Box 14)
  - Asbestos Removal, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Automation Needs, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Exhibit Area Renovation, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Facilities, 1991 (Box 15)
  - Facilities Study, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Rewiring of Reference Area, 1990 (Box 15)
  - SML Annex, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Space Available (Box 15)
  - Space, 1986-1991 (Box 15)
  - Space Needs, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Space Requirements, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Spacesaver, 1989 (Box 15)
  - YU Auditing, 1990 (Box 15)
  - YUL-Library's Special Funding Needs, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Video Archives (Box 15)
  - Testimonies (Box 16)
  - VAHT, 1983-1985 (Box 16)
  - VAHT, 1986 (Box 16)
  - VAHT, 1987 (Box 16)
  - VAHT-US Holocaust Memorial Council (Box 16)
  - Grant (Box 16)
  - Public Services (Box 16)
  - Public Services-Policies, Forms, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Public Services, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Public Services Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 17)
  - Public Services Meetings, 1986 (Box 17)
  - Public Services Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 17)
  - Public Services Meetings, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Public Services Reference Coverage, 1986-1988 (Box 17)
  - PBS (Box 17)
  - Planning Processing Priorities, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Grants (Box 17)
  - Conservation Grant Proposal, 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - NEH (Box 18)
  - NEH Grant Application, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Medical History Collection-NEH Grant Application (Box 18)
  - Medical History Collection-NEH Grant Application (Box 18)
  - NHPC (Box 18)
  - YO Medical Library, 1987 (Box 18)
  - ConferenceslWorkshops/Meeting (Box 18)
  - Archival Workshop, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Asso. of Research Libraries, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Committee on Scientific Materials and Archives, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Librarians' Conferences (Box 19)
  - Meeting at Beinecke, 1969 (Box 19)
  - New England Archivists, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Microfilms (Box 19)
  - Austrian State Archives, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Cape Political Corresp., 1969 (Box 20)
  - General, 1969-1971 (Box 20)
  - Jahn Collier Papers, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Library of Congress, 1973 (Box 20)
  - Marsh, O.C. (Box 20)
  - Massachusetts Archives (Box 20)
  - Microfilm Accessions, 1969-1970 (Box 20)